Dominic Cabitac

672 Blackwood Boulevard Oshawa, Ontario L1K0G7 Phone: 289 685 6342 Dominiccabitac@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dominic-cabitac/

https://domcabitac.github.io

February, 2019

Dear Management,

Please accept my resume for your consideration for employment at your company. Perhaps after reading this letter and resume, you will agree we have a mutually beneficial reason to meet.

I believe that I possess the characteristics that would make me a valued employee at your facility. I am currently a student at the University of Ontario Institute of Technology, pursuing my dedicated studies in the Computer Science program. I believe that I possess the characteristics that would make me a valued employee. My work in the retail and customer service field has shaped me to become a friendly, helpful and intuitive worker and to always do what is best for the company as well as the customer. My outgoing nature has brought me much success in my field and I enjoy bringing positive energy to my workplace. I am very efficient with work that needs to be done and I always help anyone who needs it. I believe that I am a quick learner and have a sharp memory, which benefits my work performance so I always give the customer the right information. I have a passion for fitness and health and I try to model good choices both at the gym and in my daily life. With my experience being a cashier and at drive-thru at McDonalds, I have learned how to deal with unhappy customers or rude customers at any time of the day. With my experience from Boathouse, I have learned how to satisfy customers by showing them the best possible deals the store has to offer. If I had to choose 3 words to describe myself it would be approachable, reliable, and confident.

This position sounds like an outstanding opportunity and a great learning experience. I would welcome the chance for an interview to discuss your needs and outline my strength in person. You may contact me at 289 685 6342 or email me at dominiccabitac@gmail.com. Thank you for your time and considering my resume. I look forward to speaking with you.

Sincerely,
Dominic Cabitac

Dominic Cabitac

672 Blackwood Boulevard Oshawa, Ontario L1K0G7 Phone: 289 685 6342

Dominiccabitac@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dominic-cabitac/

https://domcabitac.github.io

Education:

Sept 2016 – Present Bachelor of Science, Computer Science

University of Ontario Institute of Technology

Sept 2014 – Aug 2015 General Arts and Science – Science and Engineering Prep UOIT Transfer

Durham College

Work Experience:

Nov 2014 – Present Support Staff, Boathouse

• Sales Floor Associate

Cashier

Shoes Associate

Stock

Apr 2017 – Aug 2017 Labourer, Thursty Pools

Pool installation

Maintenance Services

Oct 2012 – Nov 2014 Crew Trainer Candidate, McDonalds

• Front Counter Cashier / Drive Thru

Grill/ Meal Preparation Table

Stock

Volunteer Experience:

2014 Usher, Monsignor Paul Dwyer C.S.S

• Usher for our rendition of "Footloose" the musical

Guide people to their seats

• Sell refreshments during the break

2012 Organizer, Saint Joseph The Worker Church

Organized annual Family Day celebration

• Planned out games, prizes and special contests for families

Baker, Monsignor Paul Dwyer C.S.S

 Participated in bake sale to raise funds for refugees in 3rd world countries

Organized selling dates, time and location

• Cooked the bake goods

2011 Coach, Saint John Bosco Catholic School

• Co-coached senior boys basketball team

• Organized drills and scrimmages

• Helped plan out practice dates, times and tournaments

Achievements/Awards:

2014 – 2016 Durham College General Arts and Science – Science and Engineering

Representative

2015 Durham College Alumni

Mar 2013, Sept 2013 McDonalds Employee of the Month

Jun 2010 Saint John Bosco's Male Athlete of the Year

References Available upon request